planetdestiny.com 2019-05-22

# Privacy Policy | PlanetDestiny.com

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which PlanetDestiny collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the planetdestiny.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by PlanetDestiny.

Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website’s web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user’s IP address, which is automatically recognized by our web servers.

### Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### Cookies

This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.

### Non-personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### How we use Collected Information

PlanetDestiny may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * **_To improve customer service_**  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * **_To improve our Site_**  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * **_To send periodic emails_**  
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

### How we Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing Your Personal Information

We **do not** sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### Third Party Websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

### Changes

PlanetDestiny has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site and revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### DestinyLFG.net

DestinyLFG.net does not sell or trade your user information in any way, shape or form. Your data is stored on the DestinyLFG.net database. The personal information stored is your PSN ID and/or Xbox Live Gamertag, language, comment, class, level, activity selected and IP address. Your PSN ID or Xbox Live Gamertag, language, comment, class, level and activity selected are used to display your listing; your IP address is stored for security purposes.

[divider]

## Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

**destinygamenews@gmail.com**
